Bessett, Ryan M. Under Review. "The role of phonology in discerning lone other-language items as borrowing or codeswitches: Evidence from Southern Arizona Spanish". Language Variation and Change.

Bessett, Ryan M. To appear Nov 2017. “Exploring the phonological integration of lone other-language nouns in the Spanish of Southern Arizona.” U. Penn Working Papers in Linguistics, 23(2).

Kim-2019 F0 peak displacement