Good work, Jiawei. Not a question but rather a couple of suggestions. In your examination of the previous literature, be sure to clearly distinguish between studies that examine CS (as a natural bilingual practice) vs. those that look at language switching (as a experimentally induced practice). Also, I'm not sure if you mentioned this, but plan to collect data on both participants' code-switching behaviors and their exposure. That could prove very useful when you examine your results.

Finally, regarding the comments on cues to code-switching, be sure to review Jorge's from UF's work (and his students).. there's a lot there to look at. I think you're familiar with some of it... (Valdes Kroff).

2 different items in the screen